<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/tag/news-and-updates/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2021-01-21T22:39:08-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://localhost:4000/tag/news-and-updates/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">Ron Becker | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>CyberSec, SysAdmin, DevOps, and more.</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Please Be Patient</title>
      <link href="http://localhost:4000/please-be-patient" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Please Be Patient" />
      <published>2021-01-19T04:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2021-01-19T04:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <id>http://localhost:4000/please-be-patient</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/please-be-patient">&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-are-doing-a-bit-of-a-remodel&quot;&gt;We are doing a bit of a remodel&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, I really hope that you can be patient with it. I have grabbed a new Jekyll theme based on the default theme for ghost. And, it’s amazing! But, it does take a little effort to get the hang of. For me at least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, please, just give it a day or two, and then all should be done and ready.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>ronbecker</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="News and Updates" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">We are doing a bit of a remodel</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Hello, World!</title>
      <link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello, World!" />
      <published>2021-01-18T04:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2021-01-18T04:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <id>http://localhost:4000/welcome</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome">&lt;h2 id=&quot;youre-probably-wondering-where-the-hell-youve-ended-up&quot;&gt;You’re probably wondering where the hell you’ve ended up.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s a very, very good question. Now is your chance to run off to Google, or Reddit. Go ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, you actually stuck around? I’m sorry… now you are doomed to reading this garbage. Well, since you’re here I may as well explain who I am, and what I plan to do around here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-name-is-ron-becker&quot;&gt;My name is Ron Becker&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, I love to learn about, talk about, and share information about a variety of fields. You may run across posts covering everything from CyberSec, SysAdmin, Linux, Web Development, and more. My interests, and hobbies are luckily pretty varied. Unlike my skill set… I have been working with computers, coding, and various IT and SysAdmin jobs for the last 12 years or so. Surprisingly I still suck at it all, and don’t know very much. But, this blog is how I intend to change that. If I force myself to write about and use the knowledge I gather I hope that it will “stick” a little better, and I will get better at putting it into practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope that something in here will help you, or someone you know on their journey to learn more as well!&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>ronbecker</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="News and Updates" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">You’re probably wondering where the hell you’ve ended up.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
