<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/tag/linux/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2021-01-21T22:39:08-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://localhost:4000/tag/linux/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">Ron Becker | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>CyberSec, SysAdmin, DevOps, and more.</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Garuda Linux is the Answer to Everything</title>
      <link href="http://localhost:4000/garuda-linux-is-the=answer" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Garuda Linux is the Answer to Everything" />
      <published>2021-01-21T04:00:00-06:00</published>
      <updated>2021-01-21T04:00:00-06:00</updated>
      <id>http://localhost:4000/garuda-linux-is-the=answer</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/garuda-linux-is-the=answer">&lt;h2 id=&quot;i-will-admit-i-have-a-distro-addiction&quot;&gt;I will admit I have a distro addiction.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I change my Linux distro more often than most people change their underwear. There is always something new to try, or that catches my eye. Or, that used to be the case anyways. I think I have finally found the home I have been searching for in &lt;a href=&quot;garudalinux.org&quot;&gt;Garuda Linux&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-garuda-linux&quot;&gt;What is Garuda Linux?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garuda is an Arch based distro. So, you get that same feel, rolling releases, pacman, and all the other goodies. But, you get so, so much more. There is also an install tool so you don’t have to do Linux the hard way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;which-version-should-i-get&quot;&gt;Which version should I get?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many options to choose from once you get to the download page. My personal favorite is the Dragonized Gaming Edition with KDE for the desktop. Not only is it gorgeous, but it is perfect for most games that I have tried out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a wonderful distro for gaming, and multimedia. It has made full use of the MSI GE63 Raider RGB 9SE I used to test it. It plays games like Ark Survival Evolved as well as Windows ever did, and Dark Souls 3 is as smooth as butter.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>ronbecker</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Linux" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">I will admit I have a distro addiction. I change my Linux distro more often than most people change their underwear. There is always something new to try, or that catches my eye. Or, that used to be the case anyways. I think I have finally found the home I have been searching for in Garuda Linux.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
